Rakka is a action, science fiction, horror film directed by Neill Blomkamp.
A story of broken humanity following the invasion of a
technologically superior alien species.
Bleak, harrowing, and unrelenting, the humans must
find enough courage to go on fighting.
Jasper, played by Sigourney Weaver.
Amir, played by Eugene Khumbanyiwa.
Carl, played by Robert Hobbs.
Sarah, played by Carly Pope.
Nosh, played by Brandon Auret.
Politician, played by Michael Huff.
Rakka is a 2017 American-Canadian military science fiction short film
made by Oats Studios and  directed by Neill Blomkamp.
It was released on YouTube and Steam on 14 June 2017.
The film explores themes of dystopia, alien, alien
contact, evil alien, short film.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.